/**
 * Array containing questions, answers and correct answers.
 */
const questions =  [
    {
    question: "Lima is the capital of which country?",
    
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 9
  },
  {
    question: 'Buenos Aires is the capital of which country?',

    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: 'Caracas is the capital of which country?',
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 12
  },
  {
    question: 'La Paz is the capital of which country?',

    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: 'Bogota is the capital of which country?',
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 5
  },
  {
    question: 'Asuncion is the capital of which country?',
       
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 8
  },
  {
    question: 'Brasilia is the capital of which country?',
       
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: 'Quito is the capital of which country?',
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 6
  },
  {
    question: 'Georgetown is the capital of which country?',
     
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 7
  },
  {
    question: 'Paramaribo is the capital of which country?',
       
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 10
  },
  {
    question: 'Montevideo is the capital of which country?',
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 11 
  },
  {
    question: 'Santiago is the capital of which country?',
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 4
  },
  
  {
    question: 'Easter Island belongs to which country?',
       
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 4
  },
  {
    question: 'In which country will you find Machu Picchu?',
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 9
  },
  {
    question: 'Pinochet was the president of which country?',
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 4
  },
  {
    question: 'Georgetown is the capital of which country?',
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 7
  },
  {
    question: 'Fujimori was a dictator in which country?',
       
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 9
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country is the most biodiverse in the world?',
     
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country was named after Christoper Columbus?',
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 5
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country has won the Football World Cup the most times?',
       
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Which country is the world's leading source of emeralds?",
       
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 5
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country is the largest producer of coffee in the world?',
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: 'In which country is Dutch the official language',
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 10
  },
  {
    question: 'In Suriname and which other country do you drive on the left-hand side of the road?',
       
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 7
  },
  {
    question: 'Where is Pisco from?',
     
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 9
  },
  {
    question: 'Where do potatoes come from?',
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 9
  },
  {
    question: 'Which country has the largest known oil reserves?',
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 12
  }, 
  {
    question: 'Where is the largest salt flat in the world?',
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 2
  }, 
  {
    question: 'Where is Patagonia?',
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 1
  }, 
  {
    question: 'Where is the dance, Tango, from?',
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 1
  }, 
  {
    question: "Which country's name comes from the latin word for silver?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 1
  }, 
  {
    question: "Iguazu Falls is located on the border of Argentina, Brazil and which other country?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 8
  }, 
  {
    question: "Lake Titicaca is located on the border of Peru and which other country?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 2
  }, 
  {
    question: "The Galapagos Islands belong to which country?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 6
  }, 
  {
    question: "Cotopaxi, one of the world's highest active volcanoes, is located in which country ?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 6
  }, 
  {
    question: "Which country was named after the equator?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 6
  },
  {
    question: "Where is the world's tallest uninterrupted waterfall, Angel Falls, located?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 12
  },
  {
    question: "Which country has the cheapest gasoline?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 12
  }, 
  {
    question: "Which country has the most Miss Universe titles?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 12
  }, 
  {
    question: "'Arepas', a flat round cornmeal cake, are eaten in Venezuela and which other country?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 5
  },
  {
    question: "The largest lake in South America is located in which country?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 12
  }, 
  {
    question: "Which country has the highest inflation rate",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 12
  }, 
  {
    question: "Which country's name means 'Little Venice'?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 12
  }, 
  {
    question: "Which is the smallest country in South America?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 10
  }, 
  {
    question: "The Falklands War was fought between the United Kingdom and which country?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "The oldest civilization in the Americas, the Caral Supe, was located in which country?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 9
  }, 
  {
    question: "The Nazca Lines are located in which country?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 9
  }, 
  {
    question: "The Atacama Desert is located in which country?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 4
  },
  {
    question: "The rugby team that were stranded in the Andes mountains for 72 days were from which country?",
        
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Bolivia",
    choice3: "Brazil",
    choice4: "Chile", 
    choice5: "Colombia",
    choice6: "Ecuador", 
    choice7: "Guyana", 
    choice8: "Paraguay", 
    choice9: "Peru", 
    choice10: "Suriname",
    choice11: "Uruguay",
    choice12: "Venezuela",
    answer: 11
  },  
  ]

function displayHighScore() {

}

function playSounds() {
    
}

console.log("Hello from quiz");